James Ahn

portfolio / jamesahn.co

portfolio password / 123456789

ux/ui designer

jamesahn0717@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/james-ahn

(236)-512-9610

Summary of Skills

UX Design	HTML	Photoshop	Teamwork
UI Design	CSS	Illustrator	Problem Solving
Prototyping	Python	Premiere Pro	Time Management
Figma	InDesign	Lightroom	Self-Motivated

¹ year + of key experience in the travel industry, combined with a solid academic background specializing in user experience

Experience

Business and Design Mentor - Starterhacks at University of Waterloo

Jan 2020

Helped out students participating in the Starterhacks with possible ideas and how to execute them with a business mindset. With a business and design background, I was able to give some tips that I learned in the real world and how it can be used in their projects

UX/UI Design Intern - Tugolo

May 2019 - August 2019

Re-designed Tugolo's entire website using Figma to make it a more interactive and user-friendly experience for its users. I worked with another designer and three developers that brought our designs to life. I focused more on the mobile designs as it was an essential part for Tugolo's target group. I started off with wireframes and moved to high fidelity models, user testing them to other workers and gaining valuable comments

UX/UI Designer - Tastebuds

Jan 2020 - present

Currently involved in launching a startup and helping design for it. I am making adjustments on the current interface to give it a more simple and clean look. After these adjustments, I went out to ask for user feedback and modify it accordingly

Education

Honours Global Business and Digital Arts — University of Waterloo

Sept 2017 - April 2021

Exchange Program - Singapore University of Technology and Design

Sept 2019 - Dec 2019

Activities & Interests

Snowboarding Camping Hiking Travelling

Photography Videography

Snowboarding

Participated in the snowboarding club in my high school and went to provincials and won 3rd place boys snowboarding and 1st place in mixed snowboarding

Travelling

Went on exchange to Singapore and travelled to 5 different countries, adding count to the 21 countries I've travelled to

Continuously expanding my knowledge through experiencing different cultures

² years + of prototyping and design sprints for quick ideas

³ years + of working in Figma with teammates and efficiently got work done with them in an effective pace